# **Connor Cappello**

Software Engineer

(559) 281-2265 | <a href="mailto:com/connor@gmail.com">com/com/connor@gmail.com</a> | <a href="mailto:www.linkedin.com/in/connor-cappello">www.linkedin.com/in/connor-cappello</a> | <a href="https://connorcappello-devportfolio.netlify.app/">https://connorcappello-devportfolio.netlify.app/</a>

#### **SKILLS**

- Python
- Django
- AWS
- PostgreSQL
- JavaScript
- REST API's
- ReactJS
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- Git
- HTML
- CSS
- Flask
- SQL
- MongoDB

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS**

**Software Engineering Immersive** | General Assembly

June 2022 - Dec 2022

Successfully completed 500+ hours of expert-led instruction in the industry's most in-demand technologies such as JavaScript, Python, Node.js, React, and more. Developed projects include:

- <u>Airhouse-Clone</u> An inventory management dashboard on one end, a connected customer facing shop on the other. Built with Django, AWS RDS, PostgreSQL and Bootstrap.
- <u>DevMeme</u> A social media site for meme posting utilizing Django, PostgreSQL, and AWS.
   Users can post memes, customize their profiles, and interact with other users
  - Github Repository
- <u>TalkTotal</u> A chat room based site built with Python Django. Users can create or join rooms based on different topics and leave messages in each room, which other users can see
  - Github repository
- <u>SongSearch</u> Node.js app built off of Genius' API that allows user to search for any song or artist and curate a lists of their favorite or most disliked songs
  - GitHub repository
- Super Mario Saiyans a classic 2D sidescroller built with HTML5, Canvas & JavaScript
  - o GitHub repository

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## The Arc of San Diego

Python Developer

- Wrote scripts with Python/Pandas to reconcile financial data from Excel
- Developed Human Resources dashboard using Django to provide cleaner, more efficient admin capabilities

## **Peerless Lending**

August 2021 - December 2022

July 2023 - October 2023

Mortgage Loan Officer Assistant

- Developed system of automated unique client emails to improve efficiency
- Helped close over \$26 million in loans in 2022
- Developed and maintained relationships with numerous loan officers, loan processors, real estate agents, and underwriters

### **EDUCATION**

**General Assembly, Remote** 

Certificate, Software Engineering Immersive (SEI)

Dec 2022

University of California, Santa Barbara

Bachelors of Communications

June 2021